{
    "id": "d852faed37b34e8c84f9e112835f348d",
    "title": "Prepositions At, On, In, To",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Let’s go ……………… Smith’s for tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f73e0f5a4654437cbb2860c2a3ad3880"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you staring ……………. her like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "de5e3b8d617d46caa763ae825af58b9b"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works …………….. a factory.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8d7b25a2c1544e58e843b004ff010d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went ……………… Canada last year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "3fe7581f5ad34d0c882d18a67ee6a1e6"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to see my brother ………….. Canada.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d4463bdc80ff487d8a66471fe23654da"
        },
        {
            "question": "Could you shout ……………… Mary and tell her that breakfast is ready?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60e25b3603bc4b5798d735bab0190a36"
        },
        {
            "question": "Turn right ……………….. the next corner.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca7829bf7f8f4193b390344cf9f70824"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a student ……………. Oxford.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4a1082ad6dad494e9272519887be0ff2"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t many mangoes ……………. the tree.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "at",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "00b5f0494f3d494385886eda5cca0b1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Agra is ………………. river Yamuna.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1dd121038f24eb99af6d34ae2088474"
        }
    ]
}